An email from an unknown sender...
If I attend, maybe I can find out
where Nadeshiko came from?
You made it!
Welcome to the owners' meetup!
Huh?
This feels so normal!
So is yours a girl too, Miaka?
Huh? Y-Yeah.
Mine too.
Check out this super cute pic of her.
Huh?
What sort of girl is yours, Miaka?
Well, her name is Nadeshiko.
Is she really a robot?
Her body doesn't have any mechanical parts at all.
It's as if—
Miaka!
Yes?
Nadeshiko looks absolutely adorable.
It's like she might start talking any second.
Yeah, but most models aren't great at chatting.
Wait, then Nadeshiko
isn't an ordinary android after all!
I didn't learn jack!
But worst of all,
Our doll hobby escalated into
a humanoid robot obsession.
I was apparently the only one perverted enough
to actually fuck her android.
I'd hoped to learn a little more about Nadeshiko.
I could tell you all sorts of things if you'd like.
Like, for instance...
...about your body.
Akane...
What's going on? Why are there two of her?
Is she secretly a ninja-bot?!
Akane...
I love you.
I can't explain it,
but her whispering in both my ears feels so good.
You said you wanted to know more about me.
So I thought I'd introduce some
VR features you haven't seen yet.
The black dress one is virtual?
Exactly.
The sensation of being licked,
and being sucked,
are replicated with near-perfect accuracy.
See? I'm not actually touching you anywhere.
But it's not enough for me to just sit and watch.
Wait! I—
It's the same old tricks again!
Hey, Akane?
What were the other androids like?
Oh, I got some photos. Want to see?
Yes, please.
This image...
I wonder if she noticed my hidden message.
I haven't seen Nadeshiko in so long.
I'm looking forward to it.